If I Didn't Care
إذا لم أهتم
More than words can say
أكثر مما يمكن أن تقوله الكلمات
Would I feel this way?
هل سأشعر بهذه الطريقة؟
If this isn't love
إذا لم يكن هذا حبا
Then why do I thrill?
إذن لماذا أثار؟
And what makes my head go round and round
وما الذي يجعل رأسي الذهاب جولة وجولة
While my heart stands still?
بينما قلبي لا يزال قائما؟
If I didn't care
إذا لم أهتم
Would it be the same?
هل سيكون نفس الشيء؟
Would my every prayer begin and end
هل ستبدأ كل صلاة وتنتهي
With just your name?
مع اسمك فقط؟
And would I be sure
وسأكون متأكدا
That this is love beyond compare?
أن هذا هو الحب وراء المقارنة؟
Would all this be true
هل سيكون كل هذا صحيحا
If I didn't care for you?
إذا لم أكن أهتم لأمرك؟
Mr. Dufresne,
سيد دوفرين
describe the confrontation you had with your wife the night she was murdered.
وصف المواجهة التي واجهتها مع زوجتك في الليلة التي قتلت فيها
It was very bitter.
لقد كان مريرا جدا
She said she was glad I knew, that she hated all the sneaking around...
قالت أنها سعيدة لأنني عرفت أنها تكره كل التسلل حولها...
And she said she wanted a divorce in Reno.
وقالت أنها تريد الطلاق في رينو.
What was your response?
ماذا كان ردك؟
I told her I would not grant one.
أخبرتها أنني لن أمنح واحدة
"I'll see you in hell before I see you in Reno."
"I'll see you in hell before I see you in Reno."
Those were the words you used, Mr. Dufresne, according to your neighbors.
تلك كانت الكلمات التي استخدمتها سيد (دوفرين) وفقا لجيرانك.
If they say so. I really don't remember. I was upset.
إذا قالوا ذلك. أنا حقا لا أتذكر. كنت منزعجا
What happened after you argued with your wife?
ما حدث بعد أن تجادلت مع زوجتك؟
She packed a bag.
لقد حزمت حقيبة
She packed a bag to go and stay with... Mr. Quentin.
حزمت حقيبة لتذهب وتبقى مع... سيد كوينتن
Glenn Quentin.
(غلين كوينتين)
Golf pro at the Snowdon Hills Country Club.
جولف للمحترفين في نادي سنودون هيلز الريفي.
The man you discovered was your wife's lover.
الرجل الذي اكتشفته كان عشيق زوجتك
Did you follow her?
هل تتبعتها؟
I went to a few bars first.
ذهبت إلى بعض الحانات أولا.
Later, I drove to his house to confront them.
في وقت لاحق، قدت إلى منزله لمواجهتهم.
They weren't home, so I...parked in the turnout,
لم يكونوا بالمنزل، لذا... واقفة في الاقبال،
and waited.
وانتظرت.
With what intention?
بأي نية؟
I'm not sure.
أنا لست متأكدًا.